socscistatistics.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy

At socscistatistics.com the privacy of our visitors is extremely important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information collected by socscistatistics.com and its usage.

_What We Don't Do and Won't Do_  
1\. We do not collect or store any of the data that is entered into our calculators.  
2\. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.

_Log Files_  
Like many other web sites, socscistatistics.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files include IP addresses, type of browser, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, etc. However, none of this data is linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

_Cookies_  
The functionality of socscistatistics.com depends partly on the use of cookies.

**EU Law** requires that we notify users from EU countries that the site uses cookies, hence the notification that appears at the bottom of the page the first time you visit the site. If you continue to use the site, it is taken that you have consented to the use of cookies.

We use Google AdSense to serve ads when you visit our website. Google might use information - not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number \- about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your web browser. However, please note that switching off or “opting out” of cookies will mean that you may not be able to use certain features of the website.
